Hello friends welcome to the channel Sher Market
Funda, today we will see the quarterly result of ICC Love Bird Journal
Insurance has come out, let
us see a little about it that
this time the final dividend has been announced for ₹550,
let us see after that the figure is in these legs, it will be
said in tax, total income this
quarter is
5255, last quarter it was
4382 from last air it was
4636, air on air income is big,
income is big in quarter to quarter also, total
expense total expense
in quarter is 300096, last quarter it was
4805 from last air it was 3000
626, air expense is big, expenditure on water to cotton has
decreased a bit, after that we will
see the profit on period worker
profit is 436 last quarter it was
30052 last receipt cotton was 300 12, air
on air income every profit is big,
profit increase result in quarter to quarter also
and  It has been quite good, after that we will
see that the earnings per app in this
quarter have been 8.90, last quarter it was
7.89, last quarter it was 6.37, every year
on yours there has been a very good increase, there has been a
good increase in each quarter, so it has been
quite good,
thank you for watching.